<?xml version="1.0"?>
<info xmlns:xsi= "http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
      xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://apps.nextcloud.com/schema/apps/info.xsd">
    <id>breezedark</id>
    <name>Breeze Dark</name>
    <summary><![CDATA[Breeze Dark theme for Nextcloud, based on the theme by KDE]]></summary>
    <description><![CDATA[
# Breeze Dark
This is a breeze dark theme for Nextcloud, based on the Breeze Dark theme made by the KDE Project.

## Usage

After you install the theme, you need to enable it. There a two options for this, a global and a personal one.

### Global

The global option enables the theme by default for all users and unauthenticated visits. Without this option items like the login and sharing pages won't be styled. There is also an option to exclude the login page from being themed. You can find the global options here:

```
Admin settings > Theming > Breeze Dark
```

Please note that you need the Theming app enabled in Nextcloud to access the global settings.

### Personal

The personal option allows each user to set their own preference independent of how you set the global option. If the user hasn't set an option yet, they will follow the global option. You can find the personal option here:

```
Personal settings > Accessibility > Breeze Dark
```

Please note that you need the Accessibility app enabled in Nextcloud to access the personal setting.

### Custom styling

Under the Theming section in the admin settings you can add your own custom styling to the theme. Only standard CSS can be used. This custom styling will be applied whenever the theme is enabled and only affects the Breeze Dark theme.
    ]]></description>
    <version>22.0.1</version>
    <licence>agpl</licence>
    <author mail="mw@mwalbeck.org" homepage="https://github.com/mwalbeck/nextcloud-breeze-dark">Magnus Walbeck</author>
    <namespace>BreezeDark</namespace>
    <category>customization</category>
    <website>https://github.com/mwalbeck/nextcloud-breeze-dark</website>
    <bugs>https://github.com/mwalbeck/nextcloud-breeze-dark/issues</bugs>
    <screenshot>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/mwalbeck/nextcloud-breeze-dark/master/screenshot.png</screenshot>
    <dependencies>
        <nextcloud min-version="22" max-version="22"/>
    </dependencies>
    <settings>
        <personal>OCA\BreezeDark\Settings\Personal</personal>
        <admin>OCA\BreezeDark\Settings\Admin</admin>
    </settings>
</info>
